[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "5's Principle",
    "lesson_detail": 62,
    "question": "Applying this principle will reduce errors by having a robust document and version control in place this will prevent old copies of forms or  documents being sent to customers.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Threshold Limit Value (TLV) ",
    "lesson_detail": 55,
    "question": "It is an occupational exposure value recommended by ACGIH to which it is believed nearly all workers can be exposed for lifetime without affecting health.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Organizational safety and health protocol",
    "lesson_detail": 50,
    "question": "Every student must have this equipment to prevent injuries throughout the whole class.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Contact Injuries.",
    "lesson_detail": 8,
    "question": "A hazard that can be prevented by not using the workshop equiptments unless they have received a sufficient training and permission from the technician in – charge.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Fire",
    "lesson_detail": 34,
    "question": "A hazard that can be prevented by making sure the equipment should be switched off when not in use for long periods of time.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Helmet",
    "lesson_detail": 52,
    "question": "A form of protective gear worn to protect the head from injuries.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Short-Term Exposure Limit",
    "lesson_detail": 56,
    "question": "A TLV type that is the absolute exposure limit that should not be exceeded at any time",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Eye Protection",
    "lesson_detail": 52,
    "question": "Is a protective gear to prevent foreign materials from coming to the eyes.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Ceiling Limit ",
    "lesson_detail": 56,
    "question": " A TLV type that is the absolute exposure limit that should not be exceeded at any time",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Average",
    "lesson_detail": 56,
    "question": "A TLV type that is the average exposure on the basis of a 8h/day, 40h/week work schedule.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 11,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Protective Clothing",
    "lesson_detail": 52,
    "question": "A type of clothing that covers the user from neck to ankle which prevents is wearer from injuries and skin irritation.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 12,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "OHS indicators",
    "lesson_detail": 58,
    "question": "Are the requirements workers come across various health and safety hazards while working.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 13,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Sustain",
    "lesson_detail": 63,
    "question": "Also translates as do without being told. This 5's principle means training and discipline.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 14,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Set",
    "lesson_detail": 63,
    "question": "This principle means arrange all necessary items so that they can be easily selected for   use.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 15,
    "topicId": 1,
    "answer": "Standard",
    "lesson_detail": 63,
    "question": "This 5's principle means maintaining high standards in workplace organization at all times.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 16,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Soldering Iron",
    "lesson_detail": 120,
    "question": "A tool used in soldering, it supplies heat to melt the solder so that it can flow to the joint between 2 work pieces.\n",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 17,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "De - Soldering Iron/Pump",
    "lesson_detail": 120,
    "question": "It is a manually or electrical powered equipment which is used to remove solder from a wire or circuit board.\n",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 18,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Standard Screw Driver",
    "lesson_detail": 120,
    "question": "It is used to drive slotted screws, it is commonly used by everyone and commonly found in households.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 19,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Allen Wrench Key",
    "lesson_detail": 111,
    "question": "A hand tool used for driving bolts and screws with a hexagonal sockets type screw head.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 20,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Phillip’s Screw Driver",
    "lesson_detail": 111,
    "question": "A type of hand tool commonly used for driving/screwing slotted screw heads.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 21,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Wrench",
    "lesson_detail": 111,
    "question": "A tool used to provide a sufficient grip and mechanical advantage in applying torque to turn rotary fasteners such as nuts and bolts.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Side Cutter/Wire Snipper",
    "lesson_detail": 117,
    "question": "A type of pliers intended for cutting wires.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Long Nose Pliers",
    "lesson_detail": 117,
    "question": "A both cutting and holding type of pliers used to ben, ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Utility Knife",
    "lesson_detail": 114,
    "question": "A type of cutting tool used for general purposes such as opening boxes, cutting and stripping wires.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Poorly designed hand tools",
    "lesson_detail": 129,
    "question": "Too heavy, poorly balanced, with a grip that is too large, the wrong shape, or slippery — can lead to injuries of the hand, wrist, forearm, shoulder, and neck. Here are the guidelines in selecting the right tool.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Weight",
    "lesson_detail": 135,
    "question": "Often a problem with power tools and tools such as drills, hammers, and saws. If the center of gravity of a heavy tool is far from the wrist, this maximum weight should be reduced. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "topicId": 2,
    "answer": "Grip",
    "lesson_detail": 132,
    "question": "A properly designed grip helps to reduce fatigue and pain. Tools that can be used in either hand allow workers to alternate hands and the tool can be used properly by the 10 percent of workers who are left-handed. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Watt Meter",
    "lesson_detail": 217,
    "question": "An instrument for measuring in watts of any given circuit. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Volt Meter",
    "lesson_detail": 211,
    "question": "An instrument used for measuring electrical potential difference between two points in an electric circuit.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Ohm Meter",
    "lesson_detail": 215,
    "question": "Electronic instrument which is widely used to check a complete circuit or to measure the resistance of a circuit element.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 31,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Test Light",
    "lesson_detail": 203,
    "question": "A simple piece of electronic test equipment used to determine the presence or absence of an electric voltage a piece of equipment under test.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 32,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Tape Measure",
    "lesson_detail": 209,
    "question": "A flexible ruler and used to measure distance and object dimensions.=",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 33,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Micrometer",
    "lesson_detail": 205,
    "question": "It is used to measure the diameter of wire/conductors in a circuit/appliance. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 34,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Wire Gauge",
    "lesson_detail": 207,
    "question": "A measuring tool for wire diameters.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 35,
    "topicId": 3,
    "answer": "Ammeter",
    "lesson_detail": 213,
    "question": "A tool used to check wiring when surges appear to be happening frequently, especially in older homes where older wiring could be faulty.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 36,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Orthographic Projection",
    "lesson_detail": 266,
    "question": "A drawing convention that is producing an accurate working drawing of a 3D object using 3 separate 2D views from 3 different viewpoints.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 37,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Isometric Projection",
    "lesson_detail": 266,
    "question": "A drawing convention that is producing an accurate drawing of a 3D object using a combination of 30º lines for lines.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 38,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "British Standard Dimensions",
    "lesson_detail": 266,
    "question": "An internationally recognized set of rules for applying dimensions to working drawings.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 39,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Styrofoam",
    "lesson_detail": 269,
    "question": "An expanded polystyrene foam in block form suitable for modeling.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 40,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Polymer",
    "lesson_detail": 269,
    "question": "A type of plastic composed of long chains of molecules.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 41,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Square",
    "lesson_detail": 273,
    "question": "Triangular drawing instrument in two versions – one with 45º angles, the other with 30º/60º angles. Both have one 90º corner. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 42,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Craft Knife",
    "lesson_detail": 276,
    "question": "Extremely sharp modeling knife for cutting card and paper with accuracy. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 43,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Line Bending",
    "lesson_detail": 301,
    "question": "The process of heating a narrow area of a sheet of thermoplastic so that the sheet can be folded to a certain angle.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 44,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Vaccum Forming",
    "lesson_detail": 291,
    "question": "The process of heating a sheet of thermoplastic forcing it over a prepared mold and drawing out all of the air under it to creat a hallow shape.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 45,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Injection Molding",
    "lesson_detail": 298,
    "question": "The process of forcing molten plastic into a mold to create solid objects.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 46,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Wire",
    "lesson_detail": 305,
    "question": "It is used to connect the components in a circuit.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 47,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Earth",
    "lesson_detail": 305,
    "question": "It is a metal plate, water pipe, or other conductor of electricity partially buried in the earth so as to constitute and provide a reliable conductive path to the ground",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 48,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Resistor",
    "lesson_detail": 305,
    "question": "A device having resistance to the passage of an electric current.\n",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 49,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Capacitor",
    "lesson_detail": 305,
    "question": "A device used to store an electric charge, consisting of one or more pairs of conductors separated by an insulator.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 50,
    "topicId": 4,
    "answer": "Tabular",
    "lesson_detail": 321,
    "question": "A system in which size and location dimensions are given from datums or coordinates given in a table identifying features on the drawing",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 51,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Act 2004",
    "lesson_detail": 133,
    "question": " This Act was varied to include the following health and safety principles",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 52,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "All Victorian workers ",
    "lesson_detail": 134,
    "question": " Who is covered by the Act S5 and S6",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 53,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Real Time OS and Multitasking OS",
    "lesson_detail": 137,
    "question": " Computer Operating systems are broadly classified into two types, what are those?",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 54,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Character User Interface(CUI) OS",
    "lesson_detail": 139,
    "question": " It is a text-based operating system, which is used for interacting with the software or files by typing commands to perform specific tasks.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 55,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Graphical User Interface(GUI) OS",
    "lesson_detail": 139,
    "question": " It is a mouse-based operating system (Windows Operating System, LINUX), wherein a user performs the tasks or operations without typing the commands from the keyboard.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 56,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Architecture of Operating Systems",
    "lesson_detail": 139,
    "question": "  The operating systems control the hardware resources of a computer. The kernel and shell are the parts of the operating system that perform essential operations.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 57,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Memory",
    "lesson_detail": 153,
    "question": " It refers to the computer hardware devices involved to store information for immediate use in a computer; it is synonymous with the term ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 58,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Chair; Parallel",
    "lesson_detail": 173,
    "question": " Adjust the height of the _____ to achieve proper posture – your legs from the body should be close to _____ to the floor.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 59,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "System Software",
    "lesson_detail": 178,
    "question": " It is computer software designed to provide platform to other software(s).",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 60,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Boot Program",
    "lesson_detail": 179,
    "question": "  Loads the operating system into the computer's main memory or random access memory (RAM).",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 61,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Character User Interface and Graphical User Interface",
    "lesson_detail": 138,
    "question": " Normal operating system is further classified into two types: What are those?",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 62,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Shell",
    "lesson_detail": 140,
    "question": " It is a part of the software which is placed between the user and the kernel, and it provides services of the kernel.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 63,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Command Line shells",
    "lesson_detail": 140,
    "question": " It provide a command line interface while graphical line shells provide a graphical user interface.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 64,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Graphical Line Shells",
    "lesson_detail": 140,
    "question": " It provides a graphical user interface.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 65,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Kernel",
    "lesson_detail": 140,
    "question": " It is a part of a software. It is like a bridge between the shell and hardware. It is responsible for running programs and providing secure access to the machine’s hardware.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 66,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Virtual and Physical",
    "lesson_detail": 142,
    "question": " A CPU consists of two types of memory modules: What are those?",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 67,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Process Management",
    "lesson_detail": 142,
    "question": " It  is an instance of a program that is being executed.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 68,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Storage Management",
    "lesson_detail": 142,
    "question": " It is a function of the operating system that handles memory allocation of the data.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 69,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Long term scheduler; Short term scheduler; Medium term schedule",
    "lesson_detail": 142,
    "question": " The schedulers are mainly of three types:",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 70,
    "topicId": 5,
    "answer": "Hard Real-Time System",
    "lesson_detail": 142,
    "question": " It is a purely time constant system. For a hard real time operating system, finishing the tasks within deadline is very important for an efficient system performance.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 71,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Always cover sharp pointed tools w/ cork",
    "lesson_detail": 220,
    "question": " One of the Proper Care and Maintenance of Tools and Equipment is:",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 72,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Safe Use",
    "lesson_detail": 223,
    "question": " These risks can vary greatly. Above all, what matters is that whoever has to use any tool or piece of equipment as part of their job does so with care.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 73,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Correct maintenance of Tools and Equipment",
    "lesson_detail": 224,
    "question": " A further part of a health and safety strategy is to maintain tools and equipment regularly.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 74,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Law on Tools and Maintenance",
    "lesson_detail": 225,
    "question": "These requirements appear in work equipment law.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 75,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Standard Operating Procedure(SOP)",
    "lesson_detail": 249,
    "question": "It is a set of written instructions that document a\nroutine or repetitive activity followed by an organization.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 76,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Electrical testers",
    "lesson_detail": 306,
    "question": "These are used to check both AC and DC voltage, continuity, circuit problems, amperage, shorted and open circuit problems, and to make sure the voltages are correct at the electrical panel.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 77,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Continuity Testers",
    "lesson_detail": 308,
    "question": "It is a device that is powered by batteries and has a probe at on end and a cord with either an alligator clip or another probe at the other end.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 78,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Solenoid Voltage Testers",
    "lesson_detail": 312,
    "question": "It is frequently called wiggies, are multi-function testers. They are capable of testing both voltage and polarity.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 79,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "FALSE",
    "lesson_detail": 312,
    "question": " Solenoid Voltage Testers is frequently called wiggle tester, are multi-function testers. They are capable of testing both voltage and polarity.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 80,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "FALSE",
    "lesson_detail": 308,
    "question": "Continuity Testers is a device that is powered by solar and has a probe at on end and a cord with either an alligator clip or another probe at the other end.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 81,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 306,
    "question": "Electrical testers are used to check both AC and DC voltage, continuity, circuit problems, amperage, shorted and open circuit problems, and to make sure the voltages are correct at the electrical panel.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 82,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Neon Voltage Testers",
    "lesson_detail": 314,
    "question": "They are a handy testing tool, usually measuring only a few inches to a half a foot long with a light at one end of the tester and two wires with probes on the other. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 83,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "FALSE",
    "lesson_detail": 314,
    "question": "Multimeters are a handy testing tool, usually measuring only a few inches to a half a foot long with a light at one end of the tester and two wires with probes on the other. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 84,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Plug-in Circuit Analyzers",
    "lesson_detail": 316,
    "question": "This tool are great, quick electrical testers that fit easily in your pocket and test outlets with ease.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 85,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Multimeters",
    "lesson_detail": 318,
    "question": "These are the most complex electrical testers because like their name says they perform various functions of testing.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 86,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Plug-in Circuit Analyzers",
    "lesson_detail": 316,
    "question": "These testers are designed to test outlets, but only ones that have three holes, meaning ones that have a hot, neutral and a ground.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 87,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 312,
    "question": "Solenoid testers do not use batteries to power them so they are always ready to check voltage accurately.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 88,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "Two",
    "lesson_detail": 312,
    "question": "Solenoid testers have _____ wires, each with a probe, extending out of the bottom of the tester.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 89,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "One is red and the other is black",
    "lesson_detail": 312,
    "question": "What color of Solenoid testers wire?",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 90,
    "topicId": 6,
    "answer": "None of the Above",
    "lesson_detail": 286,
    "question": "These are Job Performance Standards except for  ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 91,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Butane Portable 2 in 1 Soldering Tool",
    "lesson_detail": 578,
    "question": "A lightweight, compact cordless butane soldering and hot air tool.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 92,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Tweezer Style Soldering Iron",
    "lesson_detail": 581,
    "question": "Handy tweezers with 48 Watt heating element is great for soldering/desoldering Surface Mount Devices (SMD). ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "40 Watt Soldering Kit",
    "lesson_detail": 584,
    "question": "A soldering Iron Kit features soft grip comfort handle for maximum comfort and reduced slippage.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 94,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "3-Wire 40 Watt Soldering Iron for 110 Volts",
    "lesson_detail": 587,
    "question": "Soldering iron has a three wire grounded cord set and is a portable line voltage iron which means no base station is required.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 95,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Angled, Fine Point Tweezer",
    "lesson_detail": 590,
    "question": "The flat edge can be easily angled to run parallel to the skin, to enable you to grab even fine hairs, and to pull them out more easily in the direction of the hair's growth.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 96,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Straigth, Fine Point Tweezer",
    "lesson_detail": 593,
    "question": "Straight fine-point tweezers perfect for picking and placing small electronic components on PCBs. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 97,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Nibbling Tool",
    "lesson_detail": 596,
    "question": "A tool for cutting sheet metal with minimal distortion. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 98,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Joint Box or Tee or Jointing System",
    "lesson_detail": 678,
    "question": "Connections to appliances are made through joints. These joints are made in joint boxes by means of suitable connectors or joints cutouts.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 99,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Loop In/Looping System",
    "lesson_detail": 680,
    "question": "In this method of wiring, connections to appliances are made through joints. These joints are made in joint boxes by means of suitable connectors or joints cutouts. This method of wiring doesn’t consume too much cables size.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 100,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "Wiring",
    "lesson_detail": 677,
    "question": "A process of connecting various accessories for distribution of electrical energy from supplier’s meter board to home appliances such as lamps, fans and other domestic appliances.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 101,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "NAND Gate",
    "lesson_detail": 646,
    "question": "a circuit that produces an output signal until there are signals on all of its inputs.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 102,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "NOT Gate",
    "lesson_detail": 644,
    "question": "a circuit that produces an output signal only when there is not a signal on its input.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 103,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "NOR Gate",
    "lesson_detail": 642,
    "question": "a circuit that produces an output signal only when there are no signals on any of the input connections.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 104,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "OR Gate",
    "lesson_detail": 640,
    "question": "a circuit that gives an output signal if there is a signal on any of its inputs.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 105,
    "topicId": 7,
    "answer": "AND Gate",
    "lesson_detail": 637,
    "question": "a circuit that produces an output signal only when signals are received simultaneously through all input connections.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 106,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "4 band resistor",
    "lesson_detail": 677,
    "question": " are the common type of lead resistors we usually see and use in different lab experiments and projects.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 107,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "Cleat wiring",
    "lesson_detail": 1038,
    "question": "This system of wiring comprise of ordinary VIR or PVC insulated wires (occasionally, sheathed and weather proof cable) braided and compounded held on walls or ceilings by means of porcelain cleats, Plastic or wood.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 108,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 701,
    "question": "Passive electronic components are those that do not have gain or directionality. They are also called Electrical elements or electrical components. e.g. resistors, capacitors, diodes, Inductors.true or false?",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 109,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "antenna",
    "lesson_detail": 667,
    "question": "A device which is designed to receive or transmit radio signals. It is also known as an antenna.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 110,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "Dynamic noise limiter (DNL)",
    "lesson_detail": 875,
    "question": "an audio noise reduction system originally introduced by Philips in 1971 for use on cassette decks.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 111,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "Clipping",
    "lesson_detail": 856,
    "question": "a term which many people have probably heard, but may not fully understand. Very simply, clipping of an amplifier occurs when one tries to get a larger output signal out of an amplifier than it was designed to provide.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 112,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "Bridging",
    "lesson_detail": 861,
    "question": "it  refers to configuring a two channel (stereo) amplifier to drive a single load with more power than the sum of the two original channels combined.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 113,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "Color vision",
    "lesson_detail": 882,
    "question": "it is  the ability of an organism or machine to distinguish objects based on the wavelengths (or frequencies) of the light they reflect, emit, or transmit",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 114,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "switches",
    "lesson_detail": 792,
    "question": "Components that may be made to either conduct (closed) or not (open).",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 115,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "Diodes",
    "lesson_detail": 780,
    "question": "is a device which restricts current flow in only one direction",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 116,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "FALSE",
    "lesson_detail": 885,
    "question": "luminance describes the frequency of light at a given point on the screen, or in more common terms, the color of the light to be produced at a given point.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 117,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 885,
    "question": "Luminance indicates how bright a given location on the screen is",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 118,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 810,
    "question": "Echolocation is a complex and highly evolved process that has given bats the ability to exploit an ecological niche closed to all but a few animal groups-the night sky",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 119,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "acoustic",
    "lesson_detail": 808,
    "question": "it  is the science of sound and deals with the origin of sound and its propagation, either in free space or in pipes and channels or closed spaces.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 120,
    "topicId": 8,
    "answer": "light emitting diode/LED",
    "lesson_detail": 788,
    "question": " It is a special type of PN junction diode made from semiconductors like Gallium Arsenide",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 121,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Transistors",
    "lesson_detail": 1292,
    "question": "A semiconductor device capable of amplification.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Capacitors",
    "lesson_detail": 1280,
    "question": "Components that store electrical charge in an electrical field.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Network Components",
    "lesson_detail": 1284,
    "question": "Components that use more than 1 type of Passive Component.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Resistors",
    "lesson_detail": 1276,
    "question": "Components used to resist current.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 1311,
    "question": "A series circuit connects components end to end to provide a single path for current flow. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "fixed capacitor",
    "lesson_detail": 1343,
    "question": "They offer a fixed reactance to the flow of current. They can be Mica capacitor which consists of mica as the insulating material",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Variable Capacitors",
    "lesson_detail": 1345,
    "question": "They offer capacitance which can be varied by varying the distance between the plates",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "PN Junction Diode",
    "lesson_detail": 1353,
    "question": " A simple PN junction diode consists of a p-type semiconductor mounted on an n-type semiconductor such that a junction is formed between the p and n types",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "tunnel diode",
    "lesson_detail": 1357,
    "question": "It is a heavily doped pn junction diode where the current decreases with increasing forward voltage",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Schematic nets",
    "lesson_detail": 1478,
    "question": "it  tell you how components are wired together in a circuit",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 131,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": " Looping System",
    "lesson_detail": 1520,
    "question": "This method of wiring is universally used in wiring. Lamps and other appliances are connected in parallel so that each of the appliances can be controlled individually",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 132,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Capping wiring",
    "lesson_detail": 1527,
    "question": "was famous wiring system in the past but, it is considered obsolete this days because of Conduit and sheathed wiring system. The cables used in this kind of wiring were either VIR or PVC or any other approved insulated cables.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 133,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "Lead Sheathed Wiring",
    "lesson_detail": 1533,
    "question": "The type of wiring employs conductors that are insulated with VIR and covered with an outer sheath of lead aluminum alloy containing about 95% of lead.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 134,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "FALSE",
    "lesson_detail": 1539,
    "question": "Metallic cleat are made of steel which are very strong but costly as well.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 135,
    "topicId": 9,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 1539,
    "question": "a disadvantage of having a conduit wiring is that it is hard to find defects in the wiring true or false?",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 136,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "Protective clothing",
    "lesson_detail": 1655,
    "question": "a type of clothing that covers the user from neck to ankle which prevents is wearer from injuries and skin irritation.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 137,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "REPUBLIC ACT NO. 5734",
    "lesson_detail": 1573,
    "question": "THE ELECTRONICS ANDCOMMUNICATIONS ENGINEERING ACT OF THEPHILIPPINES",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 138,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "Allen Wrenches",
    "lesson_detail": 1596,
    "question": "Used to drive bolts and screws with hexagonal sockets in their heads",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 139,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "fuse",
    "lesson_detail": 1217,
    "question": "A safety device which will 'blow' (melt) if the current flowing through it exceeds a specified value",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 140,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "transformer",
    "lesson_detail": 1930,
    "question": "A device that is used to either raise or lower voltages and currents in an electrical circuit Never touch the input and output when used to prevent from electrical shocks.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 141,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "antenna",
    "lesson_detail": 1238,
    "question": "A device which is designed to receive or transmit radio signals.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 142,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 1973,
    "question": "Solder Wick is basically just copper braid that soaks up solder when you heat it up true or false?",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 143,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": " Desoldering Machine",
    "lesson_detail": 1974,
    "question": "If you repair a lot of boards, you absolutely need a machine like this. It is basically a soldering iron with a hole in the center of the tip that is connected to a vacuum pump.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 144,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "TRUE",
    "lesson_detail": 1522,
    "question": "an advantage of a loop in wiring system is that it doesn't require any joint boxes true or false",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 145,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "nets",
    "lesson_detail": 1478,
    "question": "It is  represented as lines between component terminals",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 146,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "silicone grease",
    "lesson_detail": 1459,
    "question": "Used as a lubricant in mechanical and other moving parts Always close the tip properly to prevent from leaking.",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 147,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "Integrated Circuits",
    "lesson_detail": 1759,
    "question": "A microelectronic computer electronic circuit incorporated into a chip or semiconductor; a whole system rather than a single component",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 148,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "parallel circuit",
    "lesson_detail": 1779,
    "question": " has two or more paths for current to flow. As Kirchhoff's current law states, the sum of all the currents entering any junction is equal to the sum of all the currents leaving the same junction. ",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 149,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "Zener Diode",
    "lesson_detail": 1820,
    "question": "It is a diode made up of heavily doped p region compared to the n-region, such that it not only allows current flow in one direction",
    "question_type": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 150,
    "topicId": 10,
    "answer": "Photo Diode",
    "lesson_detail": 1826,
    "question": "It is a special type of PN junction diode whose resistance decreases when light falls on it. It consists of a pn junction diode placed inside a plastic.",
    "question_type": 1
  }
]